export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Who is known as the 'God of Cricket' in India?",
    correct_ans: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    options: ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Virat Kohli", "MS Dhoni", "Kapil Dev"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Indian cricketer is nicknamed 'The Wall'?",
    correct_ans: "Rahul Dravid",
    options: ["Rahul Dravid", "Sourav Ganguly", "Anil Kumble", "VVS Laxman"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the captain of the Indian cricket team that won the 1983 World Cup?",
    correct_ans: "Kapil Dev",
    options: [
      "Kapil Dev",
      "Sunil Gavaskar",
      "Ravi Shastri",
      "Mohinder Amarnath",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Indian cricketer has the highest individual score in a Test match?",
    correct_ans: "Virender Sehwag",
    options: [
      "Virender Sehwag",
      "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "Rohit Sharma",
      "VVS Laxman",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the first Indian cricketer to take a hat-trick in Test cricket?",
    correct_ans: "Harbhajan Singh",
    options: ["Harbhajan Singh", "Anil Kumble", "Kapil Dev", "Javagal Srinath"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Indian cricketer is known as 'Captain Cool'?",
    correct_ans: "MS Dhoni",
    options: ["MS Dhoni", "Virat Kohli", "Rohit Sharma", "Sourav Ganguly"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the first Indian batsman to score a double century in ODIs?",
    correct_ans: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    options: [
      "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "Virender Sehwag",
      "Rohit Sharma",
      "Yuvraj Singh",
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Indian bowler has the most wickets in Test cricket?",
    correct_ans: "Anil Kumble",
    options: ["Anil Kumble", "Kapil Dev", "Harbhajan Singh", "Zaheer Khan"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first Indian cricketer to score 10,000 runs in ODIs?",
    correct_ans: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    options: ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Sourav Ganguly", "Rahul Dravid", "MS Dhoni"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which Indian cricketer is known as the 'Prince of Kolkata'?",
    correct_ans: "Sourav Ganguly",
    options: ["Sourav Ganguly", "Rahul Dravid", "Virat Kohli", "Yuvraj Singh"],
  },
];
